# NANA FEBRIANA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## **PROFILE**

I have worked in information technology for 2 years as a programmer, especially web developer and backend developer. Perform as developer, analyzes and implements the needs of business analysts in suitable with functional specification document (FSD) in the form of programming code. I like challenges, learning new things and I am interested in everything especially in the field of programming.

#### CONTACT



Jl Hemat 1 no 9 Jelambar West Jakarta.



+62 82240255749



febrian.nana@gmail.com



/in/nana-febriana

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING**

Bachelor's degree computer engineering.

Telkom University 2011-2016.

#### JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL

Network Engineering.

Teknologi Informasi Pembangunan 2008-2011.

## **EXPERIENCES**

# **PT Inspiro**

Software Developer / Backend Developer / Sep 2018 - Present

Perform as a developer, analyzes and implements the needs of business analysts in suitable with functional specification document (FSD) in the form of programming code.

### 1. Reminder Project.

Develop web application using spring MVC and hibernate for internal project. Reminder Apps is application for reminder when payment is due, that are running using a scheduler.

#### 2. Avantrade Widget Implementation Danamon.

Develop REST API interfaces on WMS (wealth management system) for bridge middle office and avantrade in Danamon.

# 3. Middle Office and iWealth Enhancement for i-Reksadana BTN.

Develop REST API interfaces on WMS (wealth management system) for bridge middle office and avantrade in BTN.

# PT Lemurian Inovasi Teknologi

Software Developer / Sep 2017 – Aug 2018

# 1. Protrack Apps.

Java native android project integrate with ZK framework and SOAP web service for tracking location. Protrack apps is application tracking location for each employees, every employees can check in and checkout feature and administrator can tracking every employees if leave work.

# Hobby







## **EXPERIENCES**

- 2. Develop ESTIM (Enterprise System for Technology and Information Management) internal product.
  - Maintenances and bugs fixing ESTIM (Enterprise System for Technology and Information Management).
  - Research and development feature for ESTIM (Enterprise System for Technology and Information Management).

# **PT Murni Solusindo Nusantara**

On Job Training / Fresh Graduate / Feb – Jul 2017

# On Job Training.

Helping lead developer for develop internal product SCOP (Smart Cash One Platform) project.

#### **SKILLS**

- Concepts
  - OOP (Object Oriented Programmings)
  - MVC (Model View Controller)
  - HTTP Protocol
- Programmings
  - Java
  - Spring Framework
  - Android Native
  - JQuery
- Persistence
  - MyBatis
  - Hibernate
  - JDBC
- Database Tools
  - Oracle
  - PostgreSQL
  - Microsoft SQL Server
- Application Server
  - Tomcat
- Web services
  - REST
  - SOAP
- Others (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)

